
;=== TIF_Dflow_0A014171 ===
$DF_NEWDEBT_NOTI	Your debt is now {} Septims.

;=== _DFlowMCM ===
$DF_UPDATING	Devious Followers is updating...
$DF_UPDATE_REQUIRED	Update required - exit the MCM
$DF_WELCOME	Welcome to Devious Followers
$DF_VERSION	2.12

;--- Shared ---
$DF_0	{0}
$DF_1	{1}
$DF_2	{2}
$DF_3   {3}
$DF_0%	{0}%
$DF_1%	{1}%
$DF_2HOURS	{2} HOURS
$DF_TITLE	Devious Followers
$DF_0HOURS	{0} Hours
$DF_0DAYS	{0} Days
$DF_1DAYS	{1} Days
$DF_2DAYS	{2} Days
$DF_0LIFES	{0} Lives
$DF_0TATS	{0} Tats
$DF_ENABLED	Enabled
$DF_ENABLED_DESC	Enables this option.
$DF_SETT	Settings
$DF_PRESENT	Present
$DF_NOT_PRESENT	Not Present

$DF_NONE	none
$DF_DAYPLUS	over a day
$DF_DAYS	days
$DF_DAYLESS	under a day

$DF_YES	YES
$DF_NO	NO



$DF_ADDRUCSHE	She
$DF_ADDRLCSHE	she
$DF_ADDRUCHER	Her
$DF_ADDRLCHER	her
$DF_ADDRUCHE	He
$DF_ADDRLCHE	he
$DF_ADDRUCHIS	His
$DF_ADDRLCHIS	his

$DF_REGULAR_DEALS	Classic Deals
$DF_MODULAR_DEALS	Modular Deals

$DF_DIFF_EASIEST	Easiest
$DF_DIFF_VERY_EASY	Very Easy
$DF_DIFF_EASY	Easy
$DF_DIFF_MODERATE	Moderate
$DF_DIFF_HARD	Hard
$DF_DIFF_VERY_HARD	Very Hard
$DF_DIFF_MAXIMUM	Maximum
$DF_DIFF_CUSTOM	Custom Exponent

$DF_DAILY_DEBT	Daily Debt
$DF_PUNISH_DEBT	Punishment Debt
$DF_DEVICE_REMOVE_DEBT	Device Removal Price
$DF_INC_REMOVE_DEBT	Additional Removal Price
$DF_DEAL_DEBT_RELIEF	Deal Debt Reduction
$DF_DEAL_BUYOUT	Deal Buyout Price
$DF_DEAL_DURATION	Deal Duration
$DF_DEAL_EARLY_MULTI	Deal Early Multiplier
$DF_FOLLOWER_LIVES	Follower Lives
$DF_COST_EXPLORER	Cost Explorer

$DF_EXPLORE_DIFFICULTY	Difficulty
$DF_EXPLORE_DIFFICULTY_DESC	Set the difficulty that you want to see the full range of price-per-day values for.  Play with the values here to see how price-per day will vary with different configurations. Your active settings will not be changed unless you use the button below to update them.
$DF_EXPLORE_EXPONENT	Explore Exponent
$DF_EXPLORE_EXPONENT_DESC	If you select custom difficulty, you can set a custom exponent value here and see the resulting per-day prices. These prices are just samples, you current settings aren't changed.
$DF_EXPLORE_LO_PRICE	Level 1 Price
$DF_EXPLORE_LO_PRICE_DESC	Set the per-day fee for level-one that you want to see the full range of values for. This doesn't change your active settings.
$DF_EXPLORE_HI_PRICE	Level 101 Price
$DF_EXPLORE_HI_PRICE_DESC	Set the per-day fee for an imaginary level-one-hundred-and-one that you want to see the full range of values for. This doesn't change your active settings.
$COPY_TO_SETTINGS	Copy to Active Settings
$COPY_TO_SETTINGS_DESC	Click this if you want to copy the explorer settings to your active settings. The custom exponent will only be copied if the sample difficulty is set to custom.

$DF_BOREDOM	Follower Boredom
$DF_BOREDOM_DESC	Followers get bored if you don't take enough deals. It increments each time boredom-interval ends with insufficient deals agreed. Bored followers will also charge you an extra percentage per day, which increases every day they remain bored. Bored followers may make other trouble too.
$DF_DISCOUNT	Discount Percentage
$DF_DISCOUNT_DESC	Followers will offer a discount on their daily rate for each deal you take, but it is reduced by accumulated boredom modifiers. The final discount is capped by the discount-limit you've configured.


;--- General ---
$DF_GENERAL	General
$DF_MINIMUMCONTRACT	Minimum Contract Days
$DF_MINIMUMCONTRACT_DESC	If non-zero, you cannot dismiss your follower for at least this many days. You cannot change this value while you have a follower, so choose wisely (Default: 0 days - no minimum contract). If you're enslaved, or the mod is paused, it won't count towards meeting the contract obligation.
$DF_CONTRACTREMAIN	Contract remaining
$DF_CONTRACTREMAIN_DESC	Days remaining before you can get rid of your follower - assuming you're able to pay off your debts and deals, and aren't enslaved.
$DF_CUSTOM_CURVE	Custom Curve Value
$DF_CUSTOM_CURVE_DESC	Exponent to use for custom debt curve. 1.0 gives linear scaling. Values over 1.0 are shallower, with a sharper ramp up at high levels (easier at low levels).  Values below 1.0 create a sharp ramp up at low levels, then flatten out.

$DF_DEBTDAILY	Debt per day
$DF_IN_GOLD_CONTROL	In Gold Control
$DF_FOLLOWER_ANGRY	Follower Angry
$DF_DEBTDAILY_DESC	The amount of gold your follower will charge you per game day, just for being around.
$DF_DEBTLVLDAILY	Debt per level per day
$DF_DEBTLVLDAILY_DESC	Amount added to debt, per-day, multiplied by your level. Set to 0 for no level-based debt.
$DF_INTDAILY	Interest on debt per day
$DF_INTDAILY_DESC	The interest rate, per-day, that your follower adds to your existing debt.\n(See recalculation interval).\nAt 100% it adds around 35% every 20 minutes of real time played.
$_DFDailyDebtIncrement	% pay increase per day
$_DFDailyDebtIncrement_DESC	If your follower is bored, they will increase the daily amount you must pay, by this, each day, accumulating. It's measured as a percentage of the standard daily rate, including the per level and extra follower amounts. If your follower stops being bored, the accumulated amount is reset to zero.
$DF_DEBTPERFLW	Extra debt per follower
$DF_DEBTPERFLW_DESC	Multiplier for extra followers as a percentage of current daily payment, per follower beyond the first. It does not modify the costs scaled off base debt-per-day. e.g. At 20% with 3 followers it will multiply your final debt-per-day by 1.4\nSet to 0 to disable this.
$DF_CURRENT_DF	Your devious follower is
$DF_NO_DF	You have no devious follower
$DF_CURRENT_VANILLA	Your vanilla follower is
$DF_NO_VANILLA	You have no vanilla follower
$DF_TOGGLE_FOLLOWER_ENABLE	Enable follower as a DF
$DF_TOGGLE_FOLLOWER_DISABLE	Disable follower as a DF
$DF_TOGGLE_FOLLOWER_INVALID	NPC cannot follow
$DF_TOGGLE_FOLLOWER_IS_DF	Cannot disable
$DF_TOGGLE_FOLLOWER_DESC	Toggle whether the follower under the cursor will act as a Devious Follower (DF) or not. Cannot toggle NPCs that are not already configured as potential followers or hirelings, and cannot toggle your current DF, but can toggle other current followers.
$DF_SELECT_A_TARGET	Select a target
$DF_FOLLOWER_ENABLE	Modify if follower is Devious
$DF_TO_TOGGLE_ENABLE	to toggle enable



$DF_DAILYDEBTMODS	Daily Debt Modifiers
$DF_MAXDEBT	Enslavement threshold
$DF_MAXDEBT_DESC	Multiple of the daily debt at which your follower will enslave or severely punish you. You do not get 'enslaved' in endless mode, but restraints are added.
$DF_SLAVEFAILDEBT	Abandonment threshold
$DF_SLAVEFAILDEBT_DESC	Additional multiple of daily debt - on top of enslavement debt - at which your follower will give up and discard you.

$DF_PERCITEMSTAKEN	Percentage of items stolen
$DF_PERCITEMSTAKEN_DESC	Percentage of items stolen when you exceed max debt. This percentage is doubled in some cases.
$DF_FREEDOMPRICE	Slave value
$DF_FREEDOMPRICE_DESC	The debt assigned if you are sold via Simple Slavery or mod-event, as a multiple of the normal daily payment. It is only used it you are enslaved from outside DF.
$DF_HOURSNEXTBILL	Billing interval (hours)
$DF_HOURSNEXTBILL_DESC	Your follower will recalculate your debt this often (in hours).
$DF_FLWCDOWNDAYS	Follower event cool-down in days
$DF_FLWCDOWNDAYS_DESC	Follower event timer interval. Determines the time between events where your follower may do something based on your situation.\nIt is not advisable to set this to less than a day. Really, keep it at least 24 hours.
$DF_PUNISHDEBT	Punishment debt
$DF_PUNISHDEBT_DESC	Additional debt added for punishments as a percentage of current daily payment.
$DF_FLWLIFES	Follower lives
$DF_FLWLIFES_DESC	Lives are used up when your follower is knocked down (enters bleed-out). They are also used for device removal if your willpower is low. Restore lives by sleeping for at least six hours.
$DF_FLWVICTIMLIFELOST	Follower lives lost when victim
$DF_FLWVICTIMLIFELOST_DESC	If your follower is a victim in a sex scene, they will lose a life. (Some mods do not set the flag victim correctly).
$DF_STATS	Stats
$DF_DEBT	Debt
$DF_DEBT_DESC	How much you currently owe in debt to followers.
$DF_WILLPOWER	Willpower
$DF_WILLPOWER_DESC	Your willpower. If this goes down, your follower is more likely to take advantage of you, and you are less able to stop them. It's reduced whenever you run out of resistance. Resting restores it, and the better the sleep, the more it restores.

$DF_MIN_WILL_REGAIN	Min Will Regained
$DF_MIN_WILL_REGAIN_DESC	The minimum amount of willpower you can regain by sleeping six hours or more. Regardless of any deals, devices or modifiers, you will always gain at least this much.
$DF_MAX_WILL_REGAIN	Max Will Regained
$DF_MAX_WILL_REGAIN_DESC	The maximum amount of willpower you can regain by sleeping six hours or more. The amount gained not be more than this. The amount gained will be reduced proportional to your deal count, and devices that you wear, otherwise you will get the maximum.

$DF_RESIST	Resistance
$DF_RESIST_DESC	Your willpower's life. When depleted below zero your willpower will drop by one. It effects nothing else; willpower is the stat that controls how the mod behaves. This is the base maximum resistance. You can configure resistance per level below.

$_DFResistanceWillDelta	Resistance change/will lost
$_DFResistanceWillDelta_DESC	The change to maximum Resistance per willpower point lost. If positive, losing willpower adds maximum resistance. If negative, losing willpower reduces maximum resistance. (Default 0).
$_DFResistanceDealDelta	Resistance change/deal taken
$_DFResistanceDealDelta_DESC	The change to maximum Resistance per active deal. If positive, taking deals adds maximum resistance. If negative, taking deals reduces maximum resistance. (Default 0). Set to -1.0 to replicate the old deal toggle.

$_DFResistanceLevelDelta	Resistance change/level
$_DFResistanceLevelDelta_DESC	Add this much max-resistance per level gained. (Default 0). e.g. If you set this to 0.5, you will add 3.0 extra max-resistance at level 7. You can also set negative values, so you lose resistance as you level.

$_DFFatigue	Resistance Fatigue
$_DFFatigue_DESC	The amount of resistance that has bled away due to the follower wearing you down. Amongst other things, buying out of deals will reduce this.
$_DFFatigueRate	Resistance Fatigue Rate
$_DFFatigueRate_DESC	The amount of resistance that bleeds away each time that you pay the follower. This accumulates unless you do something to reduce it.
$_DFGoldPerFatigue	Gold/Fatigue Regain
$_DFGoldPerFatigue_DESC	Gold donation required to regain one fatigue point. Talk to priests and priestesses. Donations are always multiples of 1000 gold, but the fatigue regained varies according to this value. (Default 200 per point).
$DF_RESISTANCE_FATIGUE_LIMIT	Resistance Fatigue Limit
$DF_RESISTANCE_FATIGUE_LIMIT_DESC	This sets the maximum value for Resistance Fatigue (default 100). This limits the amount of resistance that can be lost due to 'fatigue' after sleeping. Set to 0 if you want to disable resistance fatigue. The impact of this will depend on the resistance per will you have configured.


$DF_DEBT_PER_DAY_LO	Debt per day at level 1
$DF_DEBT_PER_DAY_HI	Debt per day at level 101
$DF_DEBT_PER_DAY_LO_DESC	Debt per day at level one. Debt per day will scale between (or beyond) these values based on your level. The difficulty setting changes the scaling curve, but the low and high values still determine the actual range. If you want big debts at low levels, increase this.
$DF_DEBT_PER_DAY_HI_DESC	Debt per day at level one-hundred-and-one. This is the theoretical debt-per-day you'd have to pay at level 101, the difficulty only changes how the values are *spaced* between the level 1 value and this one. If you want big debts at high levels, increase this.

$DF_DEBT_DIFFICULTY	Debt Difficulty Curve
$DF_DEBT_DIFFICULTY_DESC	Debt Difficulty Curve. The easier settings mean that debt increases more slowly at low levels, and faster at higher levels. This effect is reduced as difficulty is increased. The max difficulty has linear debt scaling.

$DF_DEPS	Other mod tie-ins/compatability
$DF_SSLV	Simple Slavery chance
$DF_TATS	Max tats on enslave (mod needed)
$DF_FFALL	Frostfall/Hypothermia help
$DF_LOCCHANGENOTI	Location notifications
$DF_LOCCHANGENOTI_DESC	Notification of location type change
$NO_DEAL_MADE_YET	Deal inactive
$DF_BOREDOM_INTERVAL	Boredom Interval (Days)
$DF_BOREDOM_INTERVAL_DESC	The number of days between increases in follower boredom level. If follower has a boredom level over zero, they will add an extra percentage to the daily rate every day they are bored. Other things may also happen. Reduce follower boredom by taking deals or playing games.
$DF_DEAL_COUNT	Current Deals
$DF_DEAL_COUNT_DESC	The total number of deals that you currently have. Deals above stage one count as multiple deals.
$DF_EXPECTED_DEAL_COUNT	Expected Deals
$DF_EXPECTED_DEAL_COUNT_DESC	The number of deals the follower would like you to have to prevent them from becoming bored. Playing games with the follower helps reduce this.
$DF_EXPECTED_DEAL_LIMIT	Expected Deal Limit
$DF_EXPECTED_DEAL_LIMIT_DESC	Limits the highest value possible for the expected deal count. Expected deal count increases each time the boredom interval ticks over and you have enough deals for the follower not to be bored. This puts a cap on it. If you cap at zero, the follower will never be bored.


;--- Prices and Deals ---
$DF_COSTS	Costs

$DF_DEALSETT	Deal cost settings

$DF_GOLDREMDEAL	Deal removal cost
$DF_GOLDREMDEAL_DESC	Cost to remove a deal once its duration has elapsed, as a percentage of the base daily fee, ignoring any deal discounts.
$DF_DEALREMDEBT	Deal debt relief
$DF_DEALREMDEBT_DESC	Amount of debt taking a deal will remove, as a percentage of the base daily fee, ignoring any deal discounts.

$DF_DEALDUR	Deal duration (days)
$DF_DEALDUR_DESC	Standard number of days before deals become eligible for pay-off at the configured price.

$DF_EARLYREMMULT	Early removal scale %
$DF_EARLYREMMULT_DESC	Premature deal removal cost multiplier as a percentage. Scales up cost of deal removal before it's standard duration has elapsed. Set to 0 to disable.\nCostIncrease = This x DaysAheadOfSchedule x DebtCost / 100

$DF_DEEP_DEBT_DIFFICULTY	Deep Debt Cost Scale
$DF_DEEP_DEBT_DIFFICULTY_DESC	Scales the extra buyout cost added by the expensive "deep debt" deal by this amount. The *extra* cost is based on the daily debt value, x1 for a single deal stage, x3 for two deal stages, and x7 for three deal stages, scaled by this value; this is added to the normal buyout cost. Unmodified by early buyout.

$DF_GSETT	Gambling Settings
$DF_JACKPOTVAL	Jackpot value
$DF_JACKPOTVAL_DESC	Jackpot for gambling. Other gambling values are scaled based on this.
$DF_DEVREMPRICES	Device Removal Prices
$DF_DEVREMBASEPRICE	Base device removal price
$DF_DEVREMBASEPRICE_DESC	Base cost for devious item removal as a percentage of current daily payment.
$DF_PRICEINCRPERREM	Price increase per removal
$DF_PRICEINCRPERREM_DESC	How much the cost to remove items is increased after each item removal, as a percentage of current daily payment.
$DF_COSTMULTDEPT	Cost multiplier for debt vs cash
$DF_COSTMULTDEPT_DESC	Scales cost of item removal, if taking debt instead of paying immediately.
$DF_KEYGAMEDIF	Key game difficulty
$DF_KEYDIF_DESC	Difficultly/Likely hood of getting a specific key.
$DF_KEYDIF_EASY	Easy (60%)
$DF_KEYDIF_NORMAL	Normal (50%)
$DF_KEYDIF_HARD	Hard (42%)
$DF_KEYDIF_DEVIOUS	Devious (37%)
$DF_KEYDIF_SLAVE	Slave (33%)
$DF_KEYGAMECON	Conceal chance
$DF_KEYCON_DESC	Chance something in concealed in key game
$DF_REMOVAL_FULL	Normal
$DF_REMOVAL_LIMITED	Limited
$DF_REMOVAL_OFF	Off
$DF_REMOVAL_MODE	Device Removal mode
$DF_REMOVAL_MODE_DESC	Normal = Heavy bondage, gags, hood/blindfold, gloves, mittens, boots. Limited = Heavy bondage, blindfold and mittens. Off = None.
$DF_DISCOUNT_LIMIT	Discount Limit
$DF_DISCOUNT_LIMIT_DESC	The maximum percentage of discount the the daily fee obtained by taking deals. Each deal you have adds percentage discount, but once you reach the limit, additional deals provide no benefit.

;--- Punishments ---
$DF_PUNISHMENTS	Punishments

;--- Chaos Mode ---
$DF_CHAOSM	Chaos Mode
$DF_ACTIVATECM	Activate chaos mode?

$DF_ACTIVATECM_DESC	Start or stop chaos mode. Marked means chaos mode is enabled. Chaos mode will modify your existing settings, either scaling the setting, or replacing the effective value. No settings are destroyed or overwritten.
$DF_CONCELVAL	Conceal Values?
$DF_CONCELVAL_DESC	Conceals the currently active chaos mode values. If this is disabled, the current chaos values are shown at the bottom of this page. This doesn't hide anything on the main Stats page. You may need to scroll down to see them.

$DF_MAXDAILYDEBTCHANGEPERC	Max percentage change per-roll
$DF_MAXDAILYDEBTCHANGEPERC_DESC	Percentage of the new random value that will be used vs the current random value, on each re-roll. If you set this to 100%, values are completely random each re-roll. If you set to 0%, the values won't change after first roll.

$DF_DAYSTILLCHAOSREROLL	Days until chaos re-rolls values
$DF_DAYSTILLCHAOSREROLL_DESC	Minimum days until re-roll and update of the random values. It will be at least this long, and won't happen until you sleep, or your follower updates debt, so the time interval for debt payments will also impact this.

$DF_MAXDAILYDEBT	Max debt per day
$DF_MAXDAILYDEBT_DESC	Maximum scale for your daily debt. e.g. If you set this to 10.0, then your daily debt may be up to ten-times the value configured via the General page.
$DF_MINDAILYDEBT	Min debt per day
$DF_MINDAILYDEBT_DESC	Minimum scale for your daily debt. e.g. If you set this to 0.5, then your daily debt may be as low as half the vakue configured via the General page.

$DF_MAXPUNISHDEBT	Max punishment debt
$DF_MAXPUNISHDEBT_DESC	Maximum scale for punishment debt. e.g. If you set this to 5.0, then your punishment debt may be up to five times the value configured via the Costs page.
$DF_MINPUNISHDEBT	Min punishment debt
$DF_MINPUNISHDEBT_DESC	Minimum scale for punishment debt. e.g. If you set this to 0.1, then your punishment debt may be as low as one-tenth the value configured via the Costs page.

$DF_MAXDEVREMPRICE	Max device removal price
$DF_MAXDEVREMPRICE_DESC	Maximum scale for the initial device removal fee.
$DF_MINDEVREMPRICE	Min device removal price
$DF_MINDEVREMPRICE_DESC	Minimum scale for the initial device removal fee.

$DF_MAXDEVREMINCR	Max device removal Increase
$DF_MAXDEVREMINCR_DESC	Maximum scale for the additional per-device cost for device removal.
$DF_MINDEVREMINCR	Min device removal Increase
$DF_MINDEVREMINCR_DESC	Minimum scale for the additional per-device cost for device removal.

$DF_MAXDEBTREMDEAL	Max debt removed by deals
$DF_MAXDEBTREMDEAL_DESC	Maximum scale for deal debt relief. This is applied at the point you take the deal.
$DF_MINDEBTREMDEAL	Min debt removed by deals
$DF_MINDEBTREMDEAL_DESC	Minimum scale for deal debt relief. This is applied at the point you take the deal.

$DF_MAXDEALREMCOST	Max deal buyout cost
$DF_MAXDEALREMCOST_DESC	Maximum scale for deal buyout cost. This is applied at the time of buyout.
$DF_MINDEALREMCOST	Min deal buyout cost
$DF_MINDEALREMCOST_DESC	Minimum scale scale for deal buyout cost. This is applied at the time of buyout.

$DF_MAXDEALDUR	Max Deal duration
$DF_MAXDEALDUR_DESC	Maximum deal duration in days. Deal duration will vary between this and the adjacent chaos minimum value. This is used instead of the value configured in Costs.
$DF_MINDEALDUR	Min Deal duration
$DF_MINDEALDUR_DESC	Minimum deal duration in days. Deal duration will vary between this and the adjacent chaos maximum value. This is used instead of the value configured in Costs.

$DF_MAXDEALDAYMULT	Max deal day multiplier
$DF_MAXDEALDAYMULT_DESC	Maximum scale for the early buyout multiplier. This is used instead of the value configured in Costs.
$DF_MINDEALDAYMULT	Min deal day multiplier
$DF_MINDEALDAYMULT_DESC	Minimum scale for the early buyout multiplier. This is used instead of the value configured in Costs.

$DF_MAXLIFES	Max follower lives
$DF_MAXLIFES_DESC	Maximum follower lives in days. Follower lives will vary between this and the adjacent chaos minimum value. This is used instead of the value configured on the Willpower page.
$DF_MINLIFES	Min follower lives
$DF_MINLIFES_DESC	Minimum follower lives in days. Follower lives will vary between this and the adjacent chaos maximum value. This is used instead of the value configured on the Willpower page.


;--- Misc ---
$DF_SPANK_SUPPORT	Spanking Support
$DF_TATTOO_SUPPORT	Slave/Rape Tattoo Support

$DF_GOLDTHEFTSEX	Gold theft after sex
$DF_MAXGOLDSTOLEN	Max gold taken
$DF_MAXGOLDSTOLEN_DESC	Maximum percentage of gold stolen. The amount taken will vary randomly between this and the minimum percentage, before adjustment for willpower, if enabled.
$DF_MINGOLDSTOLEN	Min gold taken
$DF_MINGOLDSTOLEN_DESC	Minimum percentage of gold stolen. The amount taken will vary randomly between this and the maximum percentage, before adjustment for willpower, if enabled.
$DF_LESSWILLTHEFT	Less willpower = Less stolen?
$DF_LESSWILLTHEFT_DESC	If enabled, at 10 Willpower the settings above will be exactly as specified above. At 0 Willpower it will use only 10% of those settings.
$DF_GOLD_THEFT_DESC	If enabled, some random percentage of the PC's gold will be taken after they are in a sex scene. As a balancing feature, you can also enable an option below so that the percentage stolen decreases as willpower decreases, so weak-willed characters are robbed of less money.

;--- Other Mod Settings ---
$DF_OTHER	Other Mod settings
$DF_MAXSLAVETATS	Max tats on enslave (mod needed)
$DF_MAXSLAVETATS_DESC	When enslaved, a number of tattoos can be added. The tattoo count will be random, ranging from one, up to this number. Set to 0 to disable tattoo addition.
$DF_FFALLHELP	Frostfall/Hypothermia help
$DF_FFALLHELP_DESC	Add the ''I'm cold'' dialog option to followers. They'll have something to keep you warm...

$DF_OTHERDEALMODS	Misc mod support
$DF_LOLA_SUPPORT	Submissive Lola

$DF_INELIGIBLE	Not eligible
$DF_ENSLAVEWEIGHTS	Simple Slavery enslave in DFC
$DF_DEALENSLAVE	Deal enslavement
$DF_DEALENSLAVE_DESC	Weights for how you'll be enslaved if you are sent to DFC *from* Simple Slavery. Not to be confused with weights for how you are enslaved *by* this mod. Note that it's possible to be bounced back to DFC from Simple Slavery if your weights allow it.
$DF_NORMALENSLAVE	Normal enslavement
$DF_NORMALENSLAVE_DESC	Weight that you'll have a set of deals to pay off when you sent to this mod from Simple Slavery.
$DF_NORMALDEALENSLAVE	Normal then Deal enslavement
$DF_NORMALDEALENSLAVE_DESC	Weight that you'll be enslaved and also have a set of deals to pay off when you sent to this mod from Simple Slavery.\nThis one is the most fun by far.
$DF_FOLLOWER_FRAMEWORKS	Follower Frameworks
$DF_AFT	Amazing Follower Tweaks
$DF_AFT_PRESENT	AFT is installed and working. Your current devious follower count is shown. Non-devious followers are not counted.
$DF_EFF	Extensible Follower Framework
$DF_EFF_PRESENT	EFF is installed and working. Your current devious follower count is shown. Non-devious followers are not counted.
$DF_NFF	Nether's Follower Framework
$DF_NFF_PRESENT	NFF is installed and working. Your current devious follower count is shown. Non-devious followers are not counted.
$DF_SPANKING_AVAIL	Spanking available
$DF_SPANKING_AVAIL_DESC	Is any spanking functionality available? For spanking to work, you *must* install and enable the "DF Spank SLAL mini-pack". You can find it with on the mod page (https://www.loverslab.com/files/file/10482-devious-followers-continued/). DFC main install does not include it, it's up to you to add the pack if you want spanking.
$DF_SPANKING_ANIMS	Spanking animations
$DF_SPANKING_ANIMS_DESC	Animations found enabled: For spanking to work, you MUST install and enable all seven of the animations from the "DF Spank SLAL mini-pack", which includes animations (used with permission) from Anub, Nibbles and Rydin. If this shows PARTIAL, you have not enabled all the required animations.
$DF_SPANKING_CODE	Spank That Ass Patched
$DF_SPANKING_CODE_DESC	Has 'Spank That Ass' code been installed and patched correctly? If 'Spank That Ass' isn't installed, this will be 'NO STA'. If the patch isn't applied properly, this will still be 'UNPATCHED'. You do NOT need to install STA, but if your STA is installed AND unpatched, your log will fill with spam and spanking might not work well.
$DF_NO_STA	NO STA
$DF_STA_UNPATCHED	UNPATCHED
$DF_STA_TOO_OLD	OLD VERSION
$DF_PATCHED_OK	PATCHED OK
$DF_SKOOMA_WHORE	Skooma Whore
$DF_MME	Milk Mod Economy
$DF_SLS	SexLab Survival


$DF_NO_SEXLAB_INSTALL	MISSING SEXLAB!
$DF_SPANK_ANIMS_OK	DF SPANK - OK
$DF_SPANK_ANIMS_MISSING	DF SPANK - MISSING!
$DF_SPANK_ANIMS_PARTIAL	DF SPANK - PARTIAL!
$DF_SPANK_ANIMS_EDITED	DF SPANK - EDITED!

;--- Debug ---
$DF_CLICK_ME	CLICK
$DF_WORKING	WORKING
$DF_DONE	DONE
$DF_DEBUG	Debug
$DF_DOPTIONS	Debug Options
$DF_MODPAUSED	Mod Paused
$DF_MODPAUSED_DESC	When checked this mod is paused: all states are frozen and no events occur. Unpausing enables the mod and resumes updates. Pause when DF events might conflict with other content.
$DF_RESET	Reset
$DF_RESET_DESC	Resets Devious Followers mod and its internal quest states to default starting values.
$DF_READDSLAVEDEV	Re-add devices required for slavery
$DF_READDSLAVEDEV_DESC	If you've been a naughty slave and lost some (or all) of the slave devices your follower gave you, press this to get them back.
$DF_BLOCKDIAL	Blocking dialogue
$DF_BLOCKDIAL_DESC	Enabling this will use the old style of dialogue may be useful if dialogue bugs out.
$DF_DEBUGADDFLW	Debug for adding follower
$DF_DEBUGADDFLW_DESC	Adds a dialogue to all NPCs in the game to flag them as a Devious Follower. ONLY use the dialogue on a follower!
$DF_ADD100DEBT	Add 100 debt
$DF_ADD100DEBT_DESC	Add 100 debt.\nFor when you need to keep yourself honest after using another Debug function.
$DF_ADD1KDEBT	Add 1000 debt
$DF_ADD1KDEBT_DESC	Adds 1000 Debt!\nPress this a lot and have fun. There's no option to remove debt. Why would you ever want to do that?
$DF_DEBUG_RESISTANCE	Reduce resistance
$DF_DEBUG_RESISTANCE_DESC	Reduce your resistance by one point.
$DF_DEBUG_BOREDOM	Add boredom
$DF_DEBUG_BOREDOM_DESC	Add a point of boredom

$DF_SAVESETT	Save settings
$DF_SAVESETT_DESC	Save your settings.
$DF_SAVE_MSG	Save your settings?\nExisting save will be overwritten.
$DF_LOADSETT	Load setting
$DF_LOADSETT_DESC	Load your settings.
$DF_LOAD_MSG	Load settings?\nExisting settings will be replaced.

$DF_EXCLNPC	Set all NPCs non-devious
$DF_EXCLNPC_DESC	Finds potential followers in your game that aren't explicitly flagged by you and sets them to be ignored by DF. Vanilla hirelings and your current followers are not changed. Exit the MCM for it to work. It takes a little while to run, be patient. Use the option in the General page to enable or disable individual NPCs. 
$DF_IGNORE_COMPLETE_1	Bulk follower ignore completed.
$DF_IGNORE_COMPLETE_2	Manage the ignore state of individual followers using the option in DF 'General' MCM.
$DF_SUSPEND_OUTPUT_DESC	Event status.
$DF_END_SCENE	Terminate Scene
$DF_END_SCENE_DESC	Attempt to remove player from running scenes. This may repair dialog that appears to be missing, or problems where followers act strangely. Try this if your follower says you (or they) are stuck in a scene. (There is dialog for it). Not infallible, but makes a fair attempt. Can also fix issues where DFC seems not to recognize events.
$DF_REPAIR_FOLLOWER	Repair Follower
$DF_REPAIR_FOLLOWER_DESC	Attempt to fix up a follower who is added to vanilla, or a framework, but not DF, or the reverse, where an NPC has DF dialogs, but is not acting as a follower in general. Also repairs some factions. Will not fix complex problems - cross your fingers and hope.
$DF_REMOVE_FOLLOWER	Remove Follower
$DF_REMOVE_FOLLOWER_DESC	Attempt to remove your current follower. This is a HUGE CHEAT, but sometimes a player may feel this is fair to use. If you have broken dialogs or follower framework problems, it's usually an indication of a mis-installed follower framework and probably possibly a broken game.
$DF_RESTORE_CTLS	Restore Player Controls
$DF_RESTORE_CTLS_DESC	Attempt to re-enable player controls that were broken by SexLab, or a stuck scene, or numerous other things that can lock your controls. You *MUST* exit the menu after activating this.
$DF_RESTORE_CTLS_START	Attempting to restore stuck controls...
$DF_RESTORE_CTLS_END	Finished restoring controls
$DF_GET_ENSLAVED	Get Enslaved
$DF_GET_ENSLAVED_DESC	Get Enslaved
$DF_AUCTION_ME	Auction Me
$DF_AUCTION_ME_DESC	Send player for auction via Simple Slavery. If Simple Slavery is not installed, then instead the DF code for SS enslavement is called directly; there won't be an auction but you will end up enslaved. If you've never had a DF or configured an SS slaver, this may fail.


$DF_FOLLOWER_TAKE	Your follower is taking your items!
$DF_BORED_FOLLOWER	Your follower is getting bored...
$DF_CONFIDENT_FOLLOWER	Your follower grows more demanding! 

$DF_ADD_SLAVE_KIT	Fit Slave Items
$DF_ADD_SLAVE_KIT_DESC	Fit the items required for slavery: town collar, magic-mittens and boots. If you can't wear the items for some reason, they will go in your inventory instead.
$DF_ADD_CHAINS_OF_DEBT	Fit Chains of Debt
$DF_ADD_CHAINS_OF_DEBT_DESC	Add the 'chains of debt' - BlockGeneric prisoner chains that should only be removed by your follower.
$DF_ADD_BLINDFOLD	Fit Blindfold
$DF_ADD_GAG	Fit Gag
$DF_ADD_COLLAR	Fit Collar
$DF_ADD_NIP_PIERCING	Fit Nipple Piercings
$DF_ADD_BRA	Fit Chastity Bra
$DF_ADD_HOBBLE	Fit Hobble Dress
$DF_ADD_ARM_CUFFS	Fit Arm Cuffs
$DF_ADD_GLOVES	Fit Gloves
$DF_ADD_MITTENS	Fit Mittens
$DF_ADD_HEAVY_BONDAGE	Fit Armbinder
$DF_ADD_CORSET	Fit Corset/Harness
$DF_ADD_VAG_PIERCING	Fit Vaginal Piercings
$DF_ADD_VAG_PLUG	Fit Vaginal Plugs
$DF_ADD_ANAL_PLUG	Fit Anal Plug
$DF_ADD_BELT	Fit Chastity Belt
$DF_ADD_LEG_CUFFS	Fit Leg Cuffs
$DF_ADD_BOOTS	Fit Boots
$DF_ADD_PRISONER_CHAINS	Fit Prisoner Chains
$DF_ADD_PRISONER_CHAINS_DESC	Fit at set of regular prisoner chains - these are a kind of heavy bondage that covers multiple worn slots.
$DF_ADD_PET_SUIT	Fit Pet Suit
$DF_ADD_FULL_SET	Fit Full Set
$DF_ADD_FULL_SET_DESC	Fit a full set of devious items. This includes all the items that normally appear in deals, but not any special punishment items or the items from level 4 deals like the tape gag or special belt.
$DF_ADD_GENERIC_DESC	Add a generic devious item of this type using LDC. You can edit the LDC list to exclude items you don't like. Use this to fix situations where the follower is angry you aren't honoring your deal, but you can't equip the devices normally in-game, due to blocking devices, bound hands, etc. 

$DF_REMOVE_HOOD	Remove Hood
$DF_REMOVE_BLINDFOLD	Remove Blindfold
$DF_REMOVE_GAG	Remove Gag
$DF_REMOVE_COLLAR	Remove Collar
$DF_REMOVE_NIP_PIERCING	Remove Nipple Piercings
$DF_REMOVE_BRA	Remove Chastity Bra
$DF_REMOVE_HOBBLE	Remove Hobble Dress
$DF_REMOVE_ARM_CUFFS	Remove Arm Cuffs
$DF_REMOVE_GLOVES	Remove Gloves
$DF_REMOVE_MITTENS	Remove Mittens
$DF_REMOVE_HEAVY_BONDAGE	Remove Heavy Bondage
$DF_REMOVE_HEAVY_BONDAGE_DESC	Remove devious 'heavy-bondage' items. This includes yokes, armbinders, elbow-binders, front cuffs, back cuffs, prisoner-chains, straight-jackets, and pet suits. If it changes how your arms animate, it's probably heavy bondage. If removal fails, you're probably wearing a BlockGeneric or Quest item.
$DF_REMOVE_CORSET	Remove Corset/Harness
$DF_REMOVE_VAG_PIERCING	Remove Vaginal Piercings
$DF_REMOVE_VAG_PLUG	Remove Vaginal Plugs
$DF_REMOVE_ANAL_PLUG	Remove Anal Plug
$DF_REMOVE_BELT	Remove Chastity Belt
$DF_REMOVE_LEG_CUFFS	Remove Leg Cuffs
$DF_REMOVE_BOOTS	Remove Boots
$DF_REMOVE_SUIT	Remove Suit
$DF_REMOVE_SUIT_DESC	Remove a devious suit. The 'Pet Suit' is not a suit, but heavy bondage. If removal fails, you're probably wearing a BlockGeneric or Quest item.
$DF_REMOVE_GENERIC_DESC	Remove a generic devious item of this type. Use this to fix situations where the follower should probably remove the item for you, but won't due to some dialogue bug. Use the 'Add Debt' button a few times afterwards to make yourself feel less of a cheater. If removal fails, you're probably wearing a BlockGeneric or Quest item.
$DF_EXPENSIVE_DEAL	Expensive Deal
$DF_EXPENSIVE_DEAL_DESC	A deal that has 10x normal buyout cost, but otherwise has no conditions. There is no limit to the times you can get this deal. If several accumulate, the sheer magnitude of debt may be encouraing for the follower and demoralizing for you.


$DF_REMOVE_MSG_BLINDFOLD	Your follower tries to remove the blindfold.
$DF_REMOVE_MSG_BOOTS	Your follower tries to remove the boots.
$DF_REMOVE_MSG_GAG	Your follower tries to remove the gag.
$DF_REMOVE_MSG_HEAVY	Your follower tries to remove the heavy restraints.
$DF_REMOVE_MSG_MITTENS	Your follower tries to remove the bondage mittens.
$DF_REMOVE_MSG_COLLAR	Your follower tries to remove the collar.
$DF_REMOVE_MSG_GLOVES	Your follower tries to remove the gloves.



$DF_CHAOSM_MESG	By starting this mode all your Devious follower settings will be randomized to the setting below.\nWARNING you will lose your settings once chaos mode has started. Save your settings before you start it if you ever want to get them back.
$DF_EXITMENU_MSG	Please exit all Menus and wait. The process does not block you continuing with your game.
$DF_EXIT_MCM	Exit MCM now

;--- Notifications ---
$DF_DEBTADD_NOTI	Your follower has added some debt.
$DF_DEBTOVER_NOTI	Your follower is angry. You should pay them.
$DF_DEBTTIRED_NOTI	Your follower is tired and has added some debt.
$DF_TIREDADDED2_NOTI	Your follower is tired and miscounted.
$DF_NIPPELP_NOTI	As you orgasm, you feel a sharp pain in your nipples.
$DF_PIGGY_NOTI	People left to fuck: 
$DF_NOHORSE_NOTI	Your follower can't find a horse for you.

$DF_NOREST_NOTI	Your follower has added debt because they need rest.
$DF_MIN6HSLEEP_NOTI	Having less than 6 hours sleep does nothing for you or your follower.
$DF_HORSESEX1_NOTI	Your follower forces you under a horse.
$DF_HORSESEX2_NOTI	Unable to resist your pussy it starts fucking you.
$DF_HORSECONT_NOTI	You try to crawl away but it's not done with you...
$DF_HORSEEXH1_NOTI	... exhausted and in bondage ...
$DF_HORSEEXH2_NOTI	... all you can do is let the horse use you.
$DF_SLEEPTIED_NOTI	You wake up tied up. With your follower grinning deviously.
$DF_SLEEPCOUGHT_NOTI	While you were sleeping, your follower tried to tie you up, but you caught them.
$DF_WILLPOWER0_NOTI	Willpower = 0 
$DF_WILLPOWER1_NOTI	Willpower = 1
$DF_WILLPOWER2_NOTI	Willpower = 2
$DF_WILLPOWER3_NOTI	Willpower = 3
$DF_WILLPOWER4_NOTI	Willpower = 4
$DF_WILLPOWER5_NOTI	Willpower = 5
$DF_WILLPOWER6_NOTI	Willpower = 6
$DF_WILLPOWER7_NOTI	Willpower = 7
$DF_WILLPOWER8_NOTI	Willpower = 8
$DF_WILLPOWER9_NOTI	Willpower = 9
$DF_WILLPOWER10_NOTI	Willpower = 10
$DF_WAKERESTRAINT1_NOTI	You wake up, and for a second forgot you're still locked in restraints.
$DF_WAKERESTRAINT2_NOTI	As you notice them still locked on you, your heart sinks.
$DF_WAKEFREEFRESH_NOTI	You wake up feeling free and refreshed.
$DF_WAKEWILLPREST_NOTI	You reflect on your progress and feel your willpower restored.
$DF_WAKELSTRONGER_NOTI	A good night's sleep has left you feeling a little stronger.
$DF_WAKELITTLEHLP_NOTI	Even a rough night of sleep has helped a little.
$DF_PIERCSHOCK_NOTI	Your piercings shock you as your follower grins deviously.
$DF_PIERCTINGLE_NOTI	Your piercings tingle softly.
$DF_PIERCMSHOCK_NOTI	Your piercings send a massive shock through your body.
$DF_PIERCREWARD_NOTI	Your follower decides to give you a little reward.

$DF_JARLDOG1	The Jarl whistles and their dog comes over. You're unable to escape as it mounts you.
$DF_JARLDOG2	It's stops but your relief disappears as the Jarl whistles again ... it's trained for this.
$DF_JARLDOG3	Still knotted! You can't escape, and can't stop cumming. You feel broken.
$DF_JARLDOG4	The Jarl finally calls the dog off. You came like a bitch, and liked it...

$DF_JARLWHISTLE_NOTI	The Jarl whistles and calls a guard over.
$DF_JARLWHISTLEA_NOTI	The Jarl whistles again and another guard comes over... Nooo!
$DF_JARLGUARDSC_NOTI	The guard keeps going while the Jarl watches.
$DF_JARLGUARDSOFF_NOTI	The Jarl finally calls the guards off.
$DF_LIMBSSNAPBACK_NOTI	Your arms and legs snap back into bondage.
$DF_LIMBSUNSNAP_NOTI	The bindinds on your arms and legs become stretchy.

$DF_GAMEROLL1D_NOTI	You rolled a 1 
$DF_GAMEROLL2D_NOTI	You rolled a 2
$DF_GAMEROLL3D_NOTI	You rolled a 3 
$DF_GAMEROLL4D_NOTI	You rolled a 4 
$DF_GAMEROLL5D_NOTI	You rolled a 5 
$DF_GAMEROLL6D_NOTI	You rolled a 6 
$DF_NPCADDFAIL_NOTI	You're already contracted to that NPC. Pay out of DF and remove follower first.


;--PlayerAlaisDFtick Notification--
$DF_DUNGEON	Location type = Dungeon.
$DF_TOWN	Location type = Town.
$DF_DWELLING	Location type = Dwelling.
$DF_WILDERNESS	Location type = Wilderness.

$DF_DEALSTHIEF	While fucking you, your client notices your gold and helps themselves to it.
$DF_DEALSPULLED	Your follower drags you to your client.

$DF_PUNDEBT	Your follower has added some debt to punish you.
$DFNOCRED	You have used up your credit.
$DFHEADS	Heads
$DFTAILS	Tails
$DF_GOLDMOD	Gold control mode
$DF_GOLDM_DESC	Enables gold control mode, won't activate until agreed with follower or is triggered
$DF_GOLDMODMAX	Gold control Max
$DF_GOLDMODMAX_DESC	Maximum your follower will let you carry. (You can still ask for more)
$DF_GOLDMODMIN	Gold control Min
$DF_GOLDMODMIN_DESC	Minimum your follower will let you carry.
$DF_0GOLD	{0} Gold
$DFDANGER	Your debt is at a dangerous level.
$DF_LOSTALLGOLD	Because lost/spent all your gold. Your follower won't give you more.

$DF_GOLDSTAYZERO	Lose all gold lock out
$DF_GOLDKNOCKTOG	Follower bleedout tie-in
$DF_GOLDOTHERTOG	Follower life tie-in
$DF_GOLDDECAY	Gold decay per area
$DF_GOLDREDUCEMOD	Follower event tie-in loss %
$DF_STAYZERO_MODE_DESC	If the gold you are carrying hits zero when recalculating, the follower will refuse to give you any gold at all until after they have had sufficient sleep.
$DF_KNOCKDOWN_MODE_DESC	Follower entering bleedout can reduce or lock off your gold.
$DF_OTHER_MODE_DESC	When a follower life is lost through adding debt, device removal, or the keygame, there is a chance your gold can be reduced or locked off.
$DF_DECAY_MODE_DESC	The amount of gold your allowed will decay by this amount per area change.
$DF_REDMOD_MODE_DESC	Other/Knockdown can reduce your gold by this %.
$DF_GOLDCONTROLTITLE	Gold control mode

$DF_MCM_LOCKED_HEADER	Hardcore Mode Enabled - Menu Unavailable
$DF_HARDCORE_MODE	Hardcore Mode
$DF_HARDCORE_MODE_DESC	Click to enable hardcore mode. Once enabled, most MCM options will be inaccessible. There is NO OPTION TO DISABLE this; only enable this if you're certain that you have configured everything to your liking.
$DF_CLICK_TO_ENABLE	Click to Enable
$DF_SIGNCA_HEADER	Custom whore armor
$DF_SIGNCA	Custom whore armor?
$DF_SIGNCA_DESC	Use the meshes in 'meshes\armor\DFCustWhoreArmor' as your custom whore armor!
$DF_CRED2L	Credit to leave
$DF_CRED2L_DESC	Credit required to leave mode.
$DF_DEAL_BIAS	Classic vs Modular deal chance
$DF_DEAL_BIAS_DESC	The percentage chance that a classic deal will be chosen in favor of a modular deal, as long as classic deals are available. If you set this to 100%, then you will only get classic deals until there are no more left to give, after which modular deals will be offered. If you set it to 0%, then you will get only modular deals at first, and classic deals will likely be blocked due to conflicts.

$DF_SUSPENDMOD	Suspended (DF)
$DF_SUSPENDOTHER	Suspended (OTHER)
$DF_SUSPENDOK	All good!
$DF_SUSPENDOID	Event triggers
$DF_SENDRESUME	Send a resume event
$DF_SENDRESUME_DESC	Sends a "dhlp-Resume" event. "dhlp-Suspend" is sent at the start of sex events, and should stop other mods from starting their own sex scenes or rape attempts while DFC is doing things. If the resume isn't sent, it can block other mods. Sending the resume can unblock them, or DFC itself. This also unblocks the DFC event system if it seems not to be responding.

$DF_DENIAL1	You're so glad you had this belt on to protect you.
$DF_DENIAL2	After being used in bondage, you feel it would have been so much worse without the belt.
$DF_DENIAL3	You feel so very glad this belt was on. What would have happened with that creature if you didn't have it?
$DF_DENIAL4	You're quite glad this belt on, but from the moans you were making a part of you wishes it wasn't.
$DF_DENIAL5	You feel somewhat glad the belt was on but being so helpless, you've found yourself hoping they had a key.
$DF_DENIAL6	What would've happened with that creature if you didn't ... have that belt on ... No! You're not like that.
$DF_DENIAL7	Panting, you only wish that had happened with your belt off. Why is being used like that so good?
$DF_DENIAL8	Being passed around in bondage with a belt on is hell. You love it too much! You want to cum!
$DF_DENIAL9	You feel disgusted that you didn't want that to stop, instead wanted the belt to come off.

$DFANIMALCONT	Creature content
$DFANIMALCONT_DESC	Enable/Consent to animal sex used in this mod.

$DFDENSUCCESS1	Your follower makes you cum so hard, the wait was worth it. You feel satisfied.
$DFDENSUCCESS2	As you cum, your follower slows. No! You need more... Afterwards, you're still horny.
$DFDENSUCCESS3	As you came, your follower stopped. You're left desperate for more ... but the belt is back on.

$DFDENFAIL1	Your follower is happy and lets you stop.
$DFDENFAIL2	Your follower is dissatisfied and tells you to go again.
$DFDENFAIL3	Your follower doesn't think you're trying hard enough, so is going to fuck you.
$DFDENFAIL4	Your follower is satisfied, but you can't cum from just anal ... this is making you crazy.

$DFDENDOG1	The dog tries to mount you again. You need it so much you can't help but let it have its way.
$DFDENDOG2	After all this denial ... you've had one of the best orgasms of you life ... from a dog.

$DFDEALDAYINC	Your follower has added a day to a random deal.


$DF_PGDEALS	Deal options

$DF_DEALSELECT	Max stages for deals (Min 9)
$DF_DEALS_DESC	Enable/Disable this deal.

$DF_CUFFCOLLBELT	Ownership
$DF_DEALO1	Stage 3 Belt
$DF_DEALO1_DESC	Ownership deal - stage 3 enabled
$DF_DEALO2	Stage 3 Belt + Denial
$DF_DEALO2_DESC	Ownership deal - stage 3 enabled with harsher denial game
$DF_DEALOMAX_DESC	Max stage for Ownership deal.

$DF_CORSGLOVEBOOTGAG	Looking Pretty
$DF_DEALB1	Stage 3 Normal gag
$DF_DEALB1_DESC	Bondage deal - stage 3 enabled with regular gag
$DF_DEALB2	Stage 3 Tape gag
$DF_DEALB2_DESC	Bondage deal - stage 3 enabled with tape gag enforcement
$DF_DEALBMAX_DESC	Max stage for Bondage deal.

$DF_IMASLUT	Be a Slut
$DF_DEALH1	Stage 3 Arms bound
$DF_DEALH1_DESC	Slut deal - stage 3 enabled with arms/hands bound in town
$DF_DEALH2	Stage 3 Cum covering
$DF_DEALH2_DESC	Slut deal - stage 3 enabled with cum covering in town
$DF_DEALHMAX_DESC	Max stage for Slut deal.

$DF_PIERCING	Piercings
$DF_DEALPMAX_DESC	Max stage for Piercings deal.

$DF_SIGN	Plug Deal
$DFDEALSIGNTOG	Plug deal avoids HDT chain/sign.
$DFDEALSIGNTOG_DESC	Disables the HDT chain and sign in the whore deal.
$DF_DEALSQMAX_DESC	Max stage for Plug (whore) deal.



$DFNOTREMOVED	Your follower can't remove that device.
$DF_SHOWROLLS	Show Roll Messages
$DF_SHOWROLLS_DESC	Show rolls for content that have this added.
$DF_AUTOPAUSE	Auto pause on enslavement
$DF_AUTOPAUSE_DESC	Uses pause/resume on player being enslaved or released by external mods. This reacts to the ZAP framework slavery events, which are used by Simple Slavery, SD+ and Submissive Lola (optionally), and perhaps other mods. DFC won't pause if it enslaves you using its own enslavment system, because that makes no sense.


$DFPOTIONDRUNK	As you drink the foul tasting potion your follower chuckles and clears your deals
$DFPOTIONTIMERED	Not having enough gold they force you to drink a vail that will make you need them more often.
$DF_MISC	Additional Content
$DF_POTIONQUEST	Potion Quest

$DF_POTIONENABLE	Enable Potion Quest
$DFPOTIONDEALS	Number of deals needed
$DF_POTIONENABLEEVIL	Enable Forced Version
$DFPOTIONDEALSEVIL	Number deals needed
$DFPOTIONTIMERMIN	Min Timer on quest, in days.
$DFPOTIONTIMERMAX	Max Timer on quest, in days.

$DF_POTIONENABLE_DESC	The potion quest allows you to get rid of all your existing deals and debt, in exchange for drinking a potion. It probably does something nice, right? Nothing bad could ever come of such a deal...
$DFPOTIONDEALS_DESC	The minimum number of active deals needed before the regular version of the potion exchange will be offered.
$DF_POTIONENABLEEVIL_DESC	If enabled, you can be forced into drinking the potion against your will if you're wearing a collar and your willpower isn't high.
$DFPOTIONDEALSEVIL_DESC	The minimum number of active deals needed before the forced version of the potion exchange can be inflicted on you.
$DFPOTIONTIMERMIN_DESC	Minimum timer duration on quest, in days. The actual time may be less than this if you have accrued penalties.
$DFPOTIONTIMERMAX_DESC	Maximum timer duration on quest, in days.

$_DFMaxResistMCM	Maximum resistance
$_DFMaxResistMCM_DESC	The maximum your resistance can be. Confidence destroying events reduce resistance. Once it hits zero, a point of willpower is lost, and resistance is reset for the new willpower value.

$_DFMaxResistMin	Lowest max resistance
$_DFMaxResistMin_DESC	The lowest your max resistance will be after applying any adjustments. See the change per will, deals, and level below.

$_DFMaxResistDevices	DDs reduce max resistance
$_DFMaxResistDevices_DESC	Wearing certain Devious Devices reduces max resistance. Devices that do this are: collar, arm-cuffs, leg-cuffs, corset or harness, and front-cuffs (but not heavy bondage in general). These devices were chosen to give them more game-play value, and make the Chains of Debt more effective.

$_DFMaxResistDeal	Deals limit max resistance
$_DFMaxResistDeal_DESC	Deals reduce your max resistance

$_DFDealEffectWill	Deals limit max willpower
$_DFDealEffectWill_DESC	Deals limit your max willpower. Each two deals you have reduce your max willpower by one, with a limit of reduction by five.



$DF_PGMODDEALSETS	Modular Deals Settings
$DF_PGAUTOSETTING	Enabled Modular Deals

$DF_DEAL_LEVEL	Deal Level

$DFMDNoDeal	No deal
$DFMDCuffsRule	Cuffs
$DFMDCollarRule	Collar
$DFMDGagRule	Gag
$DFMDNPRule	Nipple Piercing
$DFMDVPRule	Vaginal Piercing
$DFMDNakedRule	Naked in Town 
$DFMDWhoreRule	Whore Armor
$DFMDBlindFoldRule	BlindFold
$DFMDBootsRule	Boots
$DFMDGlovesRule	Gloves
$DFMDPetSuitInTownRule	PetSuit in town
$DFMDCrawlInTownRule	Crawl in town
$DFMDInnKeeperRule	Inn keeper 
$DFMDBoundInTownRule	Tied in town
$DFMDMerchantRule	Merchant
$DFMDExpensiveRule	Deep debt deal
$DFMKeyRule	Key holder deal
$DFMSkoomaRule	Skooma drinking
$DFMMilkingRule	Forced milking
$DFMSpankRule	Beg for spanks
$DFSexRule	Offer sex
$DFMLactacidRule	Lactacid drinking
$DFMRingRule	Ring
$DFMAmuletRule	Amulet
$DFMCircletRule	Circlet


$DFMDNoDealDesc	No deal
$DFMDCuffsRuleDesc	You must wear arm and leg cuffs.
$DFMDCollarRuleDesc	You must wear a collar.
$DFMDGagRuleDesc	You must wear a gag.
$DFMDNPRuleDesc	You must wear nipple piercings.
$DFMDVPRuleDesc	You must wear vaginal piercing.
$DFMDNakedRuleDesc	You must be naked in or near towns.
$DFMDWhoreRuleDesc	You must wear whore armor.
$DFMDBlindFoldRuleDesc	You must wear a blindfold.
$DFMDBootsRuleDesc	You must wear bondage boots.
$DFMDGlovesRuleDesc	You must wear bondage gloves.
$DFMDPetSuitInTownRuleDesc	You will be made to wear a petsuit in town.
$DFMDCrawlInTownRuleDesc	You will be given an anal plug that makes you crawl in town.
$DFMDInnKeeperRuleDesc	You will be used as barter with InnKeepers.
$DFMDBoundInTownRuleDesc	You will be kept bound in and near towns.
$DFMDMerchantRuleDesc	You will be used as barter with Merchants.
$DFMDJacketRule	Jacket in town
$DFMDJacketRuleDesc	You will be kept Jacketed in and near towns.
$DFMDExpensiveRuleDesc	You will owe a large cash sum in the future.
$DFMKeyRuleDesc	Your follower will take your keys.
$DFMSkoomaRuleDesc	You must drink skooma at least three times a day.
$DFMMilkingRuleDesc	You must provide your personal milk every day, also drink Lactacid.
$DFMSpankRuleDesc	You must beg for spanking every day.
$DFSexRuleDesc	You must offer sex every day.
$DFMLactacidRuleDesc	You must drink lactacid.
$DFMRingRuleDesc	You must wear a special ring.
$DFMAmuletRuleDesc	You must wear a special amulet.
$DFMCircletRuleDesc	You must wear a special circlet.

$DF_RULE_B_1	Wear a corset
$DF_RULE_B_2	Wear gloves & slave boots
$DF_RULE_B_3	Wear a gag
$DF_RULE_B_4	Wear a tape-gag
$DF_RULE_H_1	Tell people you're a slut
$DF_RULE_H_2	Be naked in towns
$DF_RULE_H_3	Hands bound in towns
$DF_RULE_H_4	Covered in cum
$DF_RULE_O_1	Wear arm & leg cuffs
$DF_RULE_O_2	Wear a collar
$DF_RULE_O_3	Wear a chastity belt
$DF_RULE_O_4	Wear a chastity belt
$DF_RULE_P_1	Wear nipple piercings
$DF_RULE_P_2	Wear vaginal piercings
$DF_RULE_P_3	Strip to show piercings
$DF_RULE_P_4	Strip to show piercings
$DF_RULE_S_1	Wear an anal plug
$DF_RULE_S_2	Wear whore outfit
$DF_RULE_S_3	Be a whore
$DF_RULE_S_4	Be a whore


$PAUSE_DISABLED_STATS	Mod is paused...
$PAUSE_DISABLED	Disabled - mod is paused
$DF_DEALSPAGE	Deal Configuration
$DF_MODDEALSPAGE	Modular Deal Configuration
$DF_MOD1&2	Level 1 and 2 deals.
$DF_MOD3	Level 3 deals.

$DFDISABLED	Disabled
$DFENABLED	Enabled
$DFACTIVE	In Use
$DFMODDEALERROR	When altering deal setting.\n You can't remove rules while any modular deal is active. \n There has to be enough rules to meet number of deal for a setting to work.\n There is also an error catch to make sure enough deals are active in the mod. (9 rules over Old and Mod deals)
$DFMODDEALSETTIT	Settings
$DF_MODDEALNUMOFDEALS	Number of Deals to use.
$DF_BEARDEAL	Bear Deal
$DF_WOLFDEAL	Wolf Deal
$DF_DRAGONDEAL	Dragon Deal
$DF_SKEEVERDEAL	Skeever Deal
$DF_SLAUGHTERFISHDEAL	SlaughterFish Deal
$DF_DEAL1	Rule 1
$DF_DEAL2	Rule 2
$DF_DEAL3	Rule 3

$DF_STATS	Stats
$DFMDTimer	Event Timer
$DFMDTimer_Desc	How often certain deal events repeat.

$DF_LDCINITTOG	Reinit the Device Controller.
$DF_LDCINITTOG_DESC	This will reinitialize the Lozeak Device Controller that controls DDs in this mod.
$DF_CHECKDEALSMCM	Check MCM for Modular Deal Rules.


$DF_REGULAR_SLAVERY_OPTIONS	Regular Slavery Options
$DF_DISABLE_REGULAR_SLAVERY	Disable regular enslavement
$DF_DISABLE_REGULAR_SLAVERY_DESC	Your follower won't enslave you for reaching the regular enslavement debt limit. Other punishments may still apply, depending on what you configure for the 'alternate' punishment options.
$DF_SkipToTheEnd	Eager enslavement
$DF_SkipToTheEnd_DESC	If you exceed enslavement debt, you will be enslaved as soon as the follower looks for a remedy. Deals and gold control will not be considered. This has no effect if regular enslavement is disabled.

$DF_SOLD_WEIGHT	Sold Weight
$DF_REGULAR_WEIGHTS	Regular mode enslavement weights
$DF_DFCSLAVECHANCE	DFC built-in enslavement weight
$DF_SSLVCHANCE	Simple Slavery enslavement weight
$DF_LOLACHANCE	Become a Lola enslavement weight

$DF_PUNISHMENT_BENEFITS	Punishment Benefits
$DF_PUNISHMENT_DEBT_REDUCTION	Lola Debt Reduction
$DF_PUNISHMENT_DEAL_REDUCTION	Deal Reduction
$DF_SIMPLE_SLAVERY_INTEGRATION	Simple Slavery Integration

$DF_PUNISHMENT_DEBT_REDUCTION_DESC	The minimum percentage of your debt that will be removed after being punished by Submissive Lola enslavement. More debt may be removed in some cases. In other cases, all debt is removed, such as when you are sent to Simple Slavery, or when you must pay it all off yourself to leave slavery.

$DF_PUNISHMENT_DEAL_REDUCTION_DESC	The number of deals that will be removed after being punished with a special outcome. In you are sent to Simple Slavery auction all your debts are removed, but if you're returned to DFC from SS, then you may get new debts, depending on your configuration of enslavement from SS.

$DF_DFCSLAVECHANCE_DESC	Weight (0 to 100) for possibility of using "traditional" built-in DFC enslavement mechanics when enslaved by your follower due to exceeding the enslavement debt limit. If you manage to get out of slavery, you will return to your existing deals.
$DF_SSLVCHANCE_DESC	Weight (0 to 100) for the possibility that you will be sold via Simple Slavery auction if you exceed the enslavement debt limit. (If Simple Slavery is installed). Your existing deals and debts will be forgotten.
$DF_LOLACHANCE_DESC	Weight (0 to 100) for possibility of being forced into Submissive Lola enslavement when enslaved by your follower due to exceeding the enslavement debt limit. (If SLTR is installed). If you manage to get out of Lola slavery you will return to your existing deals and DF.

$DF_ALTERNATE_PUNISHMENTS	Alternative punishments
$DF_SOLDACTIVE	Alternate punishments enabled
$DFSOLDTIMERMIN	Min safety period
$DFSOLDTIMERMAX	Max safety period
$DFSOLDDEALS	Deals to start timer

$DF_SOLDACTIVE_DESC	Enabling this allows the PC to be sold or enslaved, regardless of whether regular debt enslavement is enabled or disabled. It triggers punishment based on how many deals you have instead of how much debt, and it has a safety period, with a warning before the actual punishment will occur.
$DFSOLDTIMERMIN_DESC	The lower limit of the time the PC must stay in excess of the deals limit before they can be sold or enslaved. The final time before you can be enslaved is randomly determined between this and the upper limit.
$DFSOLDTIMERMAX_DESC	The upper limit of the time the PC must stay in excess of the deals limit before they can be sold or enslaved. The final time before you can be enslaved is randomly determined between this and the lower limit.
$DFSOLDDEALS_DESC	If you have at least this many deals, a timer starts. When it runs down you can be punished. This provides a buffer that isn't present in regular mode, which may imposed enslavement any time you exceed the configured debt threshold.

$DF_ALTERNATE_WEIGHTS	Alternate punishment weights
$DF_ENDLESS_SOLD_WT_DESC	The weight (0 to 100) of being sold directly to another follower as a slave (using DFC slavery). If you get out of slavery, you will return to your existing deals, but not your old follower.
$DF_ENDLESS_SLAVE_WT_DESC	The weight (0 to 100) for the alternate slavery outcome to select regular 'built-in' DFC slavery as a punishment.
$DF_ENDLESS_AUCT_WT_DESC	The weight (0 to 100) of being sold at auction via Simple Slavery. (If Simple Slavery is installed). Your existing deals and debts will be forgotten.
$DF_ENDLESS_LOLA_WT_DESC	The weight (0 to 100) of being forced into Submissive Lola Slavery by your follower. If you manage to get out of Lola slavery you will return to your existing deals and DF.

$DF_SSLVNPCSLAVER	Set as Simple Slavery buyer
$DF_SSLVNPCSLAVER_DESC	If there is a targeted NPC, who is a potential follower, they will be set as the target owner for the Devious Followers' Simple Slavery outcome (enslavement *in* to DF, not other mods). If they aren't eligible, instead of the NPC name you'll see "NOT ELIGIBLE".




$DFDEAL_B1_HUM	Your jaw aches and you're reminded your mouth is just a sex toy for your follower.
$DFDEAL_B2_HUM	Watching your follower sweat. You shudder knowing you'll be the one to clean them.
$DFDEAL_O1_HUM	The belt holds you tightly and you wonder when your master will use you.
$DFDEAL_O2_HUM	Feeling horny, you think about how your follower tricked you into fucking a dog.
$DFDEAL_H1_HUM	Seeing townspeople, you squirm thinking about being naked, tied and telling them your a slut.
$DFDEAL_H2_HUM	You smell semen and realize it's coming from you. You wish your follower would let be clean.
$DFDEAL_P_HUM	Seeing the town, you think about how you need to show your piercings just talk to someone.
$DFDEAL_S_HUM	Feeling a little cold you want to cover up, but it reminds you how you've been tricked into being a whore.

$DFDEAL_PET_HUM	Your legs and arms ache and your mind wanders back to when people watched you crawl in that awful pet suit.
$DFDEAL_CRAWL_HUM	You can't forget that you must crawl in town, like a dumb animal.
$DFDEAL_INN_HUM	Your follower whored you out, just for some ale. That's all you're worth?
$DFDEAL_BOUND_HUM	You're always kept bound in town, just a helpless possession.
$DFDEAL_MERC_HUM	Your follower turned you into a whore just for a discount. You must be worthless.
$DFDEAL_JACK_HUM	The jacket makes you helpless in town. You need to stay close to your follower to avoid being prey.
$DFDEAL_EXPENSE_HUM	You must pay your follower so much to get free. It's impossible. You will never be able to part from them now.

$DF_SPANKING	Spanking
$DF_SPANKING_COOLDOWN	Spanking Cooldown
$DF_SPANKING_COOLDOWN_DESC	Spanking cooldown time in hours. You will not be offered the opportunity to get spanked more often than this. If you set to 0.00, then spanking will always be available, assuming other conditions are met. If you change this, any current cooldown is expired.

$DF_OBSOLETE_SETTINGS	Your settings file has no version and pre-dates DF 2.12.1\nSettings older than this cannot be cleanly restored. Some restored values have been overwritten with safe defaults.

$DF_ALLOW_FORCESTART	Allow force start
$DF_ALLOW_FORCESTART_DESC	If enabled, and you have low willpower, then a guard may cuff you and demand you choose a potential follower to act as your master, making them into a Devious Follower with outstanding debt. After disabling you may need to exit the MCM.

$DF_MILKING_NOTICE	Your follower notices you got milked.
$DF_MILKING_NO_MILKS	You didn't produce any milk bottles. Bad cow!
$DF_MILKING_ONE_MILK	You produced only one bottle. You're not a very good cow.
$DF_MILKING_FOLLOWER_DRINKS	Your follower drinks some of your milk.
$DF_MILKING_BOTTLE_TAKEN	Your follower took a bottle of your milk.
$DF_KEYS_ALL_TAKEN	Your follower took all your keys!
$DF_ZERO_LIVES	Your follower does not like being bound!

$DF_SEX_PREFERENCES	Sex scene gender preference
$DF_SEX_PREFERENCE_OPTION	Prefer
$DF_SEX_PREFERENCE_OPTION_DESC	Pick "MALES", "FEMALES", or "BOTH" from the drop-down. This will only restrict sex in scenes where random NPCs are chosen; it won't limit your follower's gender or stop them having sex with you if you didn't pick it here. Some deals may not support this yet either.
$DF_SEX_PREFER_MALE	Males
$DF_SEX_PREFER_FEMALE	Females
$DF_SEX_PREFER_BOTH	Both
$DF_DISMISSAL	Follower Dismissal
$DF_DISMISSAL_RESTRICTION	Dismissal restrictions
$DF_DISMISSAL_RESTRICTION_DESC	Limitations on paying off and dismissing devious followers. NONE: dismiss anywhere. LOCATION: only dismiss in gated city streets/inns/player-homes. WILL+LOCATION: like location but relaxed for high willpower. This option has no effect on non-devious followers.
$DF_DISMISSAL_NONE	None
$DF_DISMISSAL_WILL_OR_LOCATION	Will or Location
$DF_DISMISSAL_LOCATION	Location

$DF_SLS_HEADER	SexLab Survival Support
$DF_LICENSE_ENABLE	Handle SLS Licenses
$DF_LICENSE_FORCED	Forced Licenses
$DF_LICENSE_BASE_PRICE	License Base Price (Gold)
$DF_LICENSE_MARKUP	License Markup (%)
$DF_LICENSE_ENABLE_DESC	If enabled, you can ask the follower to look after your license purchases for you. Licenses will cost DFC debt instead of solid cash and are always 'short term'.
$DF_LICENSE_FORCED_DESC	License management can be automatically imposed by your follower, for instance, when in gold control. If not enabled you must ask the follower for help with license management before it will start.
$DF_LICENSE_BASE_PRICE_DESC	The base cost of buying a license if the follower is getting them for you. In this case, all licenses cost the same amount. That's just the deal the follower is offering, take it or leave it (default 100).
$DF_LICENSE_MARKUP_DESC	An additional markup cost added, per license, on top of the base cost for each license bought. It is based on a percentage of the current daily debt amount. You can set a value from 0% to 200% (default 10%).


$DF_UNPAUSED	Devious Followers Unpaused

$DF_HELP	Help
$DF_HELP_HEADER	Devious Followers Help Topics

$DF_CLICK_TO_READ	Read It

$DF_ABOUT_INTRO_1	Introduction
$DF_ABOUT_INTRO_2	Dismissing Followers
$DF_ABOUT_DEBT_1	About Debt
$DF_ABOUT_DEALS_1	About Deals
$DF_ABOUT_WILL_1	About Willpower 
$DF_ABOUT_RESISTANCE_1	About Resistance
$DF_ABOUT_LIVES_1	About Lives
$DF_ABOUT_SLEEP_1	About Sleep
$DF_ABOUT_GAMES_1	About Bondage Games
$DF_ABOUT_DEVICES_1	About Devices
$DF_ABOUT_DEVICES_2	About Device Removal
$DF_ABOUT_DEVICES_3	About Specific Devices
$DF_ABOUT_GOLDCONTROL_1	About Gold Control (pt 1)
$DF_ABOUT_GOLDCONTROL_2	About Gold Control (pt 2)
$DF_ABOUT_GAMBLING_1	About Gambling Games
$DF_ABOUT_BOREDOM_1	About Boredom
$DF_ABOUT_FATIGUE_1	About Resistance Fatigue
$DF_ABOUT_CHAOS_1	About Chaos Mode
$DF_ABOUT_PAUSE_1	About Pause Mode
$DF_ABOUT_DEAL_CONFIG_1	About Deal Configuration
$DF_ABOUT_ENSLAVEMENT_1	About Enslavement
$DF_ABOUT_ENSLAVEMENT_2	About Leaving Enslavement
$DF_ABOUT_EXCLUSION_1	About Exclusion
$DF_ABOUT_EXCLUSION_2	Exclude by default

$DF_ABOUT_INTRO_1_DESC	Click the different help topics to see more information about each one. Mousing over each item also provides some basic information... like this.
$DF_ABOUT_INTRO_2_DESC	Devious Followers can't be dismissed if you have contract remaining, or you owe them money. They can't be killed either.
$DF_ABOUT_DEBT_1_DESC	Every day your follower charges you for their services, adding debt. If you don't pay off the debt promptly, the follower may find other ways to recover their money.
$DF_ABOUT_DEALS_1_DESC	If you can't afford to pay your follower, you can make a deal to reduce your current debt level. It will require you to do something humiliating until you can pay off the debt.
$DF_ABOUT_WILL_1_DESC	Willpower is a stat belonging to Devious Followers. It ranges from 10 down to 0. If you have a willpower of 10, the follower's only power is to add debt. As your willpower gets lower, the follower gains more control over you.
$DF_ABOUT_RESISTANCE_1_DESC	Resistance is reduced when you do humiliating things or you submit to others. If you lose all your resistance you lose a point of willpower and resistance is reset.
$DF_ABOUT_LIVES_1_DESC	Lives are a stat belonging to Devious Followers. Your follower loses a life if they enter bleedout. If their lives go down to zero, they won't help you (much) until they have slept for at least six hours straight.
$DF_ABOUT_SLEEP_1_DESC	Sleeping restores some willpower and all lives. If *you* sleep, your follower *always* sleeps too, but your follower can also sleep without you, in which case they get their lives back, but you get no willpower.
$DF_ABOUT_GAMES_1_DESC	Sometimes your follower will spring a little "game" on you. Chances are it will be sexy and humiliating, and involve putting restraints on you against your will.
$DF_ABOUT_DEVICES_1_DESC	Your follower may expect you to wear restraints as a result of a deal. If you don't wear them you will be fined. The restraint doesn't have to be locked, and usually only has to be the right type, not a specific device.
$DF_ABOUT_DEVICES_2_DESC	Your follower can help you remove certain restraints, but they will charge for it. You can make deals that require that you wear restraints. You can buy replacement devices from your follower.
$DF_ABOUT_DEVICES_3_DESC	You can make deals that require that you wear *specific* items - usually not restraints. If you lose them, you can buy replacement items from your follower.
$DF_ABOUT_GOLDCONTROL_1_DESC	Your follower can take control of your gold. You carry a fixed amount, and the follower adjusts it. If you gain gold, the follower takes it to reduce debt. If you lose gold, you're given more but your debt goes up.
$DF_ABOUT_GOLDCONTROL_2_DESC	The fixed amount you can carry usually goes down during the day. It's reset when you sleep, and at that point your follower will let you know your real debt and credit.
$DF_ABOUT_GAMBLING_1_DESC	Your follower will let you gamble for money, or for restraint keys. The odds are not in your favor.
$DF_ABOUT_BOREDOM_1_DESC	If you keep paying off your debt promptly, it's no fun for the follower and they will get bored. Bored followers charge more for their services and are more inclined to play pranks on you.
$DF_ABOUT_FATIGUE_1_DESC	If you constantly rely on your follower it gradually erodes your self-confidence, impairing your maximum resistance after you sleep. You can make donations to the divines to feel better about yourself.
$DF_ABOUT_CHAOS_1_DESC	Chaos mode changes the settings of your game for you on a regular basis, so things are less predictable. You can configure the ranges they change in, or make all or just some values not change at all.
$DF_ABOUT_PAUSE_1_DESC	Pause mode suspends DF and turns your devious follower back into a normal follower, who you may dismiss as usual. This is useful when another mod is incompatible with DF. When you unpause, your deals and debt come back.
$DF_ABOUT_DEAL_CONFIG_1_DESC	Classic and Modular deals each have their own configuration pages. You can disable any deals you don't like, but don't disable too many or DFC won't work very well.
$DF_ABOUT_ENSLAVEMENT_1_DESC	If your fail at paying your debts your body may be used as collatoral.  The follower may use you to make money, or sell you to another follower.  It can also be a chance to pay off your debts.
$DF_ABOUT_ENSLAVEMENT_2_DESC	You have to pay off your entire debt to leave slavery. You also need to get out of gold control to make the final payment, which may require significant credit.
$DF_ABOUT_EXCLUSION_1_DESC	If you don't want a follower to become devious, and instead want them to be a normal follower, you can exclude them from the mod by targeting them and clicking a button in the 'General' MCM.
$DF_ABOUT_EXCLUSION_2_DESC	If you want all followers excluded from DF by default, then you can use an option in the 'Debug' MCM to automatically set all potential followers ignored. You can then enable just the followers you want.